[theme music playing]
[Jepoy] You don't have to
shoulder everything.
-We aren't leaving.
-Ana, this is my fight.
You mean our fight. We all want justice.
[Ivy] Now that you revealed Ana
as Lily Cruz,
I need to rush the wedding!
[Emilia] We can join forces
to finally end Lily Cruz.
Julio, I'm sorry. Your cancer is back.
[Julio] If I'm going to die,
Arnaldo's wedding has to push through.
Because he will need Ivy Aguas.
[Anna] Why will you marry that monster?
[Ivy] Just trust in my plan.
Don't try to stop my wedding
or any of my plans.
-You're worried I'll lose too.
-Yes!
[Julio shouts] Get your act together!
Arnaldo, Ardiente is yours for the taking!
Poblacion Ardiente is yours!
Grandpa, I promise I won't waste
this second chance you've given me.
Make my dream come true, my son.
[Ivy] As we talked about earlier,
after my wedding, you need to leave.
-But Ivy, you don't--
-We understand, Ivy.
[Anna] Just make sure that
Nanny Carlota's killer pays.
[Julio] Let's be close to
each other once again.
You need me. I need you.
This family needs you.
Okay, Papa. What do you want me to do?
[Julio] Lily Cruz.
[Camia] Are you sure you're safe, dear?
I can't let something bad happen to you.
[Diego] If you're pretending
to be Lily Cruz,
you need to learn everything about her.
[Jepoy] Wait a minute.
You don't want Ivy
to marry Arnaldo either, right?
You already know my answer to that.
There's no guarantee…
that I'll be safe,
or that nothing will ever happen to me.
But, Mom, I know…
you always pray for me.
That's why I know
we're going to win against the Ardientes.
Okay, dear.
I'm agreeing to all of this now.
[dramatic music playing]
But promise me
you won't keep any secrets
from me anymore.
You have to tell me everything.
Yes, Mom.
If that's what you want.
Thank you, dear.
Thank you so much.
So, Jaguar is now out of the picture?
No, Auntie.
Jaguar is the picture.
What?
You expect me to follow what Papa said?
That I'll be an obedient daughter
doing whatever he wants me to do?
Do you actually believe
he'll give the reward
he was talking about?
They're all lies, Auntie.
That's why I'm still
going to work on Jaguar.
Emilia, believe me.
Stay with Julio. Go for the familiar evil.
The thing is, Aunt Claire,
I feel different for this Jaguar.
This is something new.
I have this feeling
that he'll take care of me.
Or he'll take you to hell!
Oh, that's exciting then!
Emilia, tell me.
Do you like Jaguar?
Aunt Claire, I'm just a woman.
-I have weaknesses too.
-Oh my goodness.
You know, I crave
for a powerful man's attention,
which I'm getting from Jaguar right now.
So, can you blame me?
You're too old for this, Emilia.
-Please.
-Oh no, Auntie.
Being desired doesn't stop
until you're 70.
Now you know!
So if I have to use my body
to get that Jaguar,
I'll do it, Auntie.
-Emilia, you're crazy.
-[Emilia laughs]
Auntie, that's obvious.
And stubborn.
Anna.
If you're going to pretend to be Lily,
I have one condition.
Like what we discussed,
on the day of my wedding,
you need to leave.
I've already booked your tickets.
And called my secretary.
-But Ivy, you don't--
-We understand, Ivy.
-We'll leave on that day.
-[tense music playing]
Just make sure the man who
killed Nanny Carlota will pay.
[Camia] So--
Batch.
Hey, Batch.
[Marlon] Good thing you're back.
It looks like we have a visitor.
Batch, call everyone.
Miss Loring, Mister Pandoy.
Everyone, Diego's here.
Can everyone just gather around, please?
-Come on.
-Nanny, Uncle.
Of course, you already know Jepoy.
Good evening.
But…
…there's someone Aunt Camia
and I would like you to meet.
Friends…
she's finally back in Ardiente.
My daughter, Lily Cruz.
-Did you say Lily Cruz?
-Lily?
[Loring giggles]
Is that you, Lily?
-Yes, it's me.
-Oh my!
[Loring] Oh my goodness!
[pensive music playing]
Thank goodness, you're back.
I've wanted to come back
to Ardiente for so long.
I missed you all!
[Loring] We missed you too.
[Loring giggles]
Oh my goodness!
I can't believe it!
Wait, don't you miss someone else?
What about your best friend here?
[laughing]
-Nanny, stop it.
-[Ana giggles]
Of course, I missed Diego too.
Let's go.
-I thought so too!
-[Pandoy chuckles]
-[Ana and Loring giggle]
-Umm…
And of course, we're even stronger now
because my best friend is here.
She'll help in our campaign.
-Wow!
-Thank you.
I'm so glad that you're back.
You know…
We've been looking for you for so long.
Yeah, Diego's been waiting for you.
Let's just go inside and talk there.
-Diego's been looking for you.
-Come in.
-[Ana laughs]
-[Pandoy] Congratulations!
-[Camia] Thank you, Uncle.
You know, I finished
all my transactions in Manila
just because I couldn't let a day pass
without seeing you, hon.
If you ask me, I think
I'm going crazy over you.
[Arnaldo chuckles]
-Me too, hon.
-Really?
Hon, what if we speed up our wedding?
Why not do it next week?
What do you think?
Well, as much as I want to,
Grandpa and I agreed
that we have to take care
of Lily Cruz first.
-Oh.
-[tense music playing]
Why? Are you guys planning to…
silence Lily Cruz?
Unfortunately, everyone
who goes against our family
has to learn one way or another.
Lily Cruz.
Hon, is now the best time for that?
If you kill Lily Cruz,
who will people blame?
You.
"Arnaldo killed Lily Cruz."
"He's a murderer. He needs to be in jail."
"He doesn't deserve to be the governor."
Hon, do you get what I'm saying?
I get it.
I already thought of that, but…
I don't call the shots anymore.
Grandpa does, and I trust him.
But…
what if we talk to your grandfather?
You know, hon, Lily Cruz isn't a problem.
Actually, I think that Lily Cruz…
can be…
the solution to all your problems.
The solution?
How?
Hon.
Just trust me on this.
You need to support me on this.
Because I'm sure that
whatever I say to your grandfather,
I bet your mother will oppose as usual.
All right. Tell me what you need.
Later.
Hug me first.
[Arnaldo] I missed you.
I missed you so much, hon.
[tense music playing]
[Ivy] Why?
Are you guys planning
to silence Lily Cruz?
Unfortunately, everyone
who goes against our family
has to learn one way or another.
How many times will you have me killed?
The people I love
are always on your list of targets.
My father, my mother,
Nanny Carlota, Diego, and Jepoy.
And now, you want Anna killed.
I am the real Lily Cruz.
The one who'll drag you all to hell.
Because that's what you deserve.
-I'm the real Lily Cruz!
-[tense music intensifies]
[indistinct chatter]
-Here, have some coffee.
-Thank you.
[Camia sighs]
Anna.
I want to apologize in advance.
I just find it hard to trust people.
[soft piano music playing]
I was deceived by Nimfa in the past.
She got close to me
and betrayed me in the end.
I'd never do that, Miss Camia.
Ivy is my friend.
But I understand how you feel.
There's only one Lily in your heart,
and that's Ivy.
DIEGO FOR THE NEW ARDIENTE
Here are the records.
Mr. Diego is here.
Arnaldo is desperate.
-What happened?
-Why?
He's handing this out to everyone.
He's giving away money and rice.
It isn't right.
-Let me see. Wow, some rice.
-Is it fresh?
There's an envelope here too.
[Loring] Let me see.
[Pandoy laughs]
See what I mean?
He's using money to get votes.
Well, at least it's just rice and money.
I mean, if he uses bullets,
we're in trouble.
-[Loring] Yes.
-They could resort to violence.
He's so desperate.
-I can buy sardines with this.
-Come in.
Batch, they're my friends
from Ardiente News Network.
They want to interview you and Lily Cruz.
The Ardientes won't see this coming.
Lily's on her way here too, right?
Let's include her.
-Batch, come here.
-What?
Can we please leave Lily out of this?
Why?
I don't want her to be
a target of the Ardientes.
[ominous music playing]
Okay. I'll tell them.
-I'm sorry.
-Thank you.
I'm sorry but they're not ready.
Let's just do it next week. I'll call you.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
-I'm sorry.
-We'll reschedule.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
[ominous music intensifies]
Give me one.
[cell phone ringing]
I'm in position.
So, Ivy, how do you find the food?
You want more?
I can ask the maid to prepare more.
Or maybe, I suggest salad,
since you're preparing for
the big day, your wedding day.
Thank you, Emilia. You're so sweet.
[Ivy] I'm fine, thank you.
[Emilia] You're most welcome.
You know, Ivy, I am so happy
the animosity between us is finally over.
I feel so relieved.
You know, if we weren't eating,
I could've hugged you right now.
Well, me too.
It actually annoyed me
when all these doubts
and allegations were thrown against me.
[Ivy] So finally, you're enlightened.
Yeah.
I'm so happy that
we can be best friends again, like before.
Actually, we can be like sisters.
Can I call you Sis?
[Ivy and Julio laugh]
Emilia!
Emilia's cracking jokes again.
-"Sis"?
-Yeah.
[Ivy] But we've got a huge age gap.
I'm okay with calling you
my "future mother-in-law".
After my wedding to Arnaldo,
you can decide
what you'd like to be called.
I can call you "Ma," "Mom," or "Mama."
[Ivy] That's more fitting, I guess.
What do you think?
Pardon me for butting in, but…
Ivy is right, Emilia.
And I believe,
among the choices,
"Mama" would fit you just right.
-Right.
-It sounds more regal, right?
Yes! "Mama".
-You see?
-Mama Emilia.
-Yeah!
Mama Emilia.
[tense music playing]
And…
…the truth of the matter is,
I'm very happy that, finally,
both of you have decided
to bury the proverbial hatchet.
Um-hm.
[Ivy] Yes, Congressman. I'm so happy.
Emilia's great at burying things.
-What?
-[Emilia coughs]
She's good at burying…
resentment.
Oh, yeah.
Speaking of burying.
I want you to witness…
Lily Cruz being buried alive.
[ominous music playing]
I'm sure you're going to do that for us.
We're family now.
[ominous music intensifies]
[tense music playing]
Of course.
Now that I'm marrying Arnaldo…
-I'm going to be an Ardiente.
-[ominous music playing]
It's so exciting.
When exactly are you
going to get Lily Cruz?
-I can't wait.
-[Emilia giggles]
I love it. Perfect.
This is just so exciting.
In fact, I'm going to make
a phone call right now.
So, are you all ready to witness
the fall of Lily Cruz…
and Madrigal?
Because it's just one call away.
I just need to dial it.
Are you all ready?
[ominous music intensifies]
Could you just excuse me, please?
[tense music playing]
-Auntie.
-Hello, Diego.
[henchman cocks gun]
-Diego.
-You're here.
Of course, we need
to do well in our campaign.
[henchman cocks gun]
[tense music intensifies]
Hon, I guess we should tell
your grandfather about our plan.
Congressman, I have a proposal.
A proposal?
Have the posters arrived?
[Diego] Yes, Auntie.
The first batch came in.
[Camia] That's good.
[Diego] I'll ask Marlon to do
a follow-up, so?
[Camia] So we can start distributing them.
[Diego] You're right.
Lily Cruz is the public's symbol of hope.
The girl who lived
after Emilia ordered her killed.
Well, if you want to have
Lily Cruz and Madrigal killed,
who do you think
the public will blame again?
The Ardientes.
They'll point their
fingers at Arnaldo again.
We'd be committing
political suicide if we do that.
Yes. We started discussing
our plans for this Sunday.
So Congressman, Arnaldo and I figured,
maybe we should postpone the assassination
of Lily Cruz and Madrigal.
Instead, we offer a peace treaty.
A cease-fire.
A publicity stunt.
We have to make Arnaldo look good.
That's what he needs right now.
A good image to please
the public and the press.
Congressman, we'll give them freedom.
But the reality is,
it'll all just be an illusion.
[cell phone ringing]
Hello, boss?
Make it fast and make it quick, okay?
I don't want any survivors.
Do you hear me?
Yes, boss.
-All right, bye.
-What do you think, Congressman?
I have a point, right?
[clears throat]
[henchman cocks gun]
[tense music intensifies]
Hon?
What do you think?
It's all for you. It's all for Arnaldo.
Emilia.
Stop the operation.
But I just made the phone call
and it's all set.
I said stop the operation.
Papa, I already told our men
to proceed with--
Stop it now!
Can't you hear me?!
You got wax in your ears?!
Make the call.
-Now?
-Now!
I will, okay? Now.
[cell phone ringing]
Boss?
Abort.
Yes, boss.
Let's go!
[Diego] Let's start in the smaller areas.
[Camia] Right, all the
outlying neighborhoods.
-Auntie Camia.
-What?
We have to go inside.
Is there something wrong, Jepoy?
We'll be much safer inside.
Let's go.
-Jepoy is right.
-All right then.
It's all for you, hon.
Get ready, Emilia.
You, Arnaldo, and Ivy are going somewhere.
[indistinct chatter]
Everyone, listen up!
-The Ardientes are here.
-[tense music playing]
[Emilia sighs]
[slow tense music playing]
[Emilia] Oh!
Good morning!
It's indeed a good morning.
[Emilia] Wow!
Is that Lily Cruz…
Madrigal…
…Diego and Camia Cruz?
Too bad, I didn't bring my checklist,
because you would've gotten
a perfect attendance!
Wait.
So, this is where you make your plans.
But I see your HQ isn't finished yet.
The place still needs work.
Not enough money?
No worries, it works for you.
It looks so cheap.
[Emilia giggles]
What are you doing here, Emilia?
If you think we don't know
what you're up to, you're wrong.
Isn't it enough
that you sent your men here,
that you had to personally come
and scare us?
Camia, why are you so livid?
You're in such a bad mood.
You should actually be glad
that I didn't kill you.
You should thank me.
We don't trust any of you Ardientes.
Camia.
Why are you becoming such a war freak?
It clashes with your outfit.
You look so pure today.
I came here for peace and harmony.
[Camia laughs]
-Harmony?!
-Yeah.
What do you Ardientes know
about peace and harmony?
Camia.
The Ardientes aren't as bad as you think.
Yes, this is the proof.
This is a peace agreement.
From this day on,
the killing, cheating, and blackmailing
between Diego Torillo
and Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo will stop.
If you agree to it, Diego,
we're going to hold a press conference.
And we expect you to attend.
Diego?
[tense music intensifies]
What are you waiting for? A drum roll?
Just take it.
Hon.
[Ivy] Hon.
He's the only one in a bad mood today.
I'm in a good mood.
Bye, thanks.
See you!
Start the car.
Hon.
-Come here.
-Arnaldo.
Ouch! You're hurting me!
Hon, stop it!
Arnaldo!
Do you want someone else to kiss you?!
Hon.
You know, I just realized that
with this cease-fire going on,
you and Diego will have more
opportunities to grow closer.
I'm right, aren't I?
Hon, seriously?
Everything I'm doing,
the press conference, the peace agreement,
this is all for you!
Because I want to save your reputation.
I'm doing all this for you!
Because I'm all yours, Arnaldo!
When will you believe me?!
[sighs]
Okay.
I know you're jealous again.
Hon.
I'll make it up to you.
Come on.
Let's go.
I'll make it up to you.
You want me to, right?
Good grief!
What are those Ardientes up to this time?
Diego, I'll ask volunteers to
watch over our headquarters,
so the Ardientes won't
come back here ever again!
You're right, Mr. Pandoy.
We need to tighten
the security around here.
[Loring] Exactly. Right, Diego?
Diego?
Hey, Diego.
Are you listening?
Diego, don't tell me
you believe everything
that Ivy and the Ardientes said?
I mean, a press conference?
Miss Loring, Diego needs to attend.
If he doesn't, it'll reflect badly on him.
My goodness. But…
He's right, Nanny.
[Loring] All right then.
For now, I'll just
prepare something to eat.
Let me help you with that.
I'll help you too.
All right.
Diego.
What's your plan now?
I'll go there.
We all will.
We'll make peace with the Ardientes.
What if that peace treaty is just a sham?
There must be a reason why Ivy came here.
I'm sure she planned all this
for everyone's sake.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Emilia] If Ivy didn't
interfere with our plan,
Lily Cruz would've been gone by now.
Emilia, you're mad at Ivy again.
I thought you buried the hatchet?
Especially since the
peace treaty with Diego's camp
was all her idea.
It's not just that, Auntie.
You know why I'm so irritated now?
Because Papa sided with her.
I swear Auntie, you're the only
one I trust in this family.
Of course.
Don't worry, I'll always be here for you.
Thank you, Auntie. But you know what?
This press conference
is actually good for me.
Because I'll have the opportunity
to see what that Lily Cruz is up to.
Who knows? I might
find a way to bring her,
and Diego down in that event.
We just decided to have a peace agreement,
yet here you are,
with another vicious plan.
Ms. Claire, what's with Emilia?
Whatever your plan is, please stop it.
You'll just cause trouble.
Ivy, wait.
Let me just remind you
about the promise you made.
You told me:
"Don't worry, my future mother-in-law."
"We will bring down
that Lily Cruz together."
What happened now?
Did you just change your mind?
Don't tell me you're starting
to like that Lily Cruz?
Just like how you feel
something special for Diego.
[giggles]
Emilia, a promise is a promise.
You know what?
I have a new nickname for you.
Emilia "Paranoid" Ardiente-Torillo.
Want to know why you're paranoid?
Because of this!
Why don't you try wearing
one necklace at a time?
I promise you, this press conference
is for Arnaldo and for us, Ardientes.
See?
We aren't married yet,
but I already consider myself an Ardiente.
After the press conference,
then you can do whatever
you want with Lily Cruz.
And you'll be helping me.
Yes.
Okay.
Hello, Rufo.
Diego and Arnaldo will be
holding a press conference.
I need you to do something.
-[Anna] Have another sandwich.
-Thank you.
-This is so good!
-Yes, here, have some more.
-Even back in high school?
-Don't be shy.
-Where are we going later?
-Where'd you get this?
Sandwich, sir?
I know you already got three…
-…but that's not enough.
-I made that!
-It's tiring.
-I know.
[Anna giggles] Okay.
[Loring] Look at them.
-Original recipe.
-Have another sandwich.
-Thanks!
-Lily.
You've been serving us all day.
-Why don't you join us?
-Sit down, let's eat.
-It's fine, Mom. I'm still full.
-Yeah, join us.
[Anna] Let me know when you're done.
-I'll take those to the kitchen.
-All right.
Let us handle it, Lily.
You still have to go to
the press conference with Diego.
It's fine, Mr. Pandoy. This isn't much.
Lily's always been so
hardworking, even as a kid.
She always helped her parents out too,
and now she's even better
at helping out the townspeople.
You really are something, Lily.
He's right.
You're right, Nanny.
My best friend hasn't changed.
Besides, remember she helped me
lose weight when I was a kid?
-Yeah.
-[laughs]
-Diego.
-Hey, Batch.
This could be the start of something new.
-Wait, that sounds like--
-Keep it professional, Batch.
Watch what you're saying, Marlon.
They're just picking up
where they left off.
Really? Well, Miss Loring,
Mister Pandoy, this is how
you form strong bonds.
With a little…
-Marlon.
-Her mom's here.
-Marlon, I'm right here.
-Ms. Camia.
Don't worry, Ma'am.
I was just kidding around.
[Camia] Just finish your
sandwich. Come on, eat up.
[Marlon] I'll just have some
coffee. And keep quiet.
[reporter] Today, we'll witness
the Torillo brothers
signing a peace agreement,
which will start a cease-fire
between the two parties
for a peaceful election.
[tense music playing]
Thank you.
[crowd applauds]
[tense music continues playing]
Viva Ardiente.
[man] Everyone, please be seated.
You may now ask
the candidates your questions.
Thank you.
My question is for Mayor Arnaldo Torillo.
Why did you decide to agree to
a cease-fire with Diego Torillo?
Well, as you already know,
this campaign period
is turning into a circus.
There have been so many deaths
and a lot of accusations.
We all condemn those killings.
So, my beloved brother and I
decided to call it a truce
for the sake of the citizens
of Poblacion Ardiente.
[crowd applauds]
[man] Viva Ardiente!
Mr. Diego Torillo,
why did you agree
to the said peace agreement?
The safety of the public
is what's most important.
Our townspeople deserve
a peaceful election.
Thank you.
[crowd applauds]
For a peaceful election!
[crowd chants] Diego! Diego! Diego!
Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego!
Diego! Diego! Diego!
Lily!
Lily Cruz!
You're such a snob!
You know, Diego and Arnaldo
aren't the only ones
who deserve attention today.
You do too! You're a comeback kid!
Wait, hold on. Press! People!
Press! Come, over here!
Ladies and gentlemen, here's Lily Cruz!
-Oh.
-[Emilia giggles]
You aren't used to being in the limelight?
That's really sad.
Yes, I am Lily Cruz.
I've come back to Poblacion Ardiente
for my mother.
Do you plan on filing a lawsuit
against the Ardientes
like your mother did?
Yes, my mother already filed
a complaint against the Ardientes
for what they did to my family.
But the Ardientes twisted the truth.
Now, we're being more careful
about planning our next moves.
That's why for now, we will
allow the public to decide
what the most appropriate
punishment is for the Ardientes.
-Excuse us.
-Wow! Wait.
Not so fast.
Looks like you can't just
push Lily Cruz around.
Auntie, that's what you think.
I'm not done with you yet.
Hold on. Hold on.
Mayor, can you grant us an interview?
-Just a quick one.
-Of course, hon.
Sure.
Is it true your ratings dropped?
Is that why you signed a peace
agreement with your brother?
That's not true. In fact…
Things are getting out of hand,
as I said earlier.
We don't want innocent people
getting caught in this mess.
That's why my brother and I
decided to settle things,
so our town can be peaceful once again.
Okay. What are your other plans
for this successful
peaceful agreement
between you and your brother?
[Arnaldo] Other plans than that?
Well, I need to focus on my campaign.
[slow tense music playing]
Hey.
Do you have a new theme song?
Do you want to record a whole album,
so you can gaze lovingly at each other?
[Diego] You have a lot of ideas.
Why don't you run for president?
You might end up winning.
Arnaldo, what are you insinuating?
We are under one roof.
First of all, yes, I will run
for president someday.
-Good for you.
-But for now…
isn't the real Lily Cruz back?
Why don't you stay close to her,
instead of coming near Ivy?
You don't need to tell me that.
Good.
Can I trust you'll stay close
to Lily Cruz,
instead of my fiancée from now on?
Yes?
Okay, I'll take that as a yes.
Now, get out of my face.
Hon.
Hon, you just signed a peace agreement.
Why are you getting all jealous again?
I'm all yours.
I'm yours, Arnaldo.
Okay?
Okay, okay.
Auntie, Lily.
-Let's go.
-Do me a favor, Emilia.
The next time you want to talk to me,
just give it to me straight,
stop beating around the bush.
Let's stop wasting time, Emilia.
Okay. I won't waste your time.
Can I have five minutes
of your precious time?
Tell me the story of your life.
Why is it that after years
of being away from Ardiente,
you suddenly come back, out of the blue,
all poised and successful?
Let me guess.
Is this like a "rags to riches" story?
Or like the ones I read in the books
where the girl sells her body
in exchange for wealth?
Don't be rude!
[tense music playing]
Then tell me the truth!
Who are you, really?
Are you deaf, Emilia?
How many times do I need
to tell you that I'm Lily Cruz?!
I was orphaned, but I soldiered on.
I got an education.
I found a good job,
that's why I have a decent life.
I'm not an Ardiente like you.
But that's actually a good thing
because I actually pity you
since that's all you have.
And if you weren't an Ardiente,
you'd be worse than a rotting fish
being swarmed by maggots.
You better watch your tongue!
First of all, you have no right
to speak to my daughter that way!
Second, you have no right
to strike my daughter's face
with that filthy hand of yours!
Both of you, please remember:
I'm not done with you yet.
You won't get away with this!
You will burn in hell!
That's enough, Emilia!
Your days of torturing Lily
and her family are over.
Why, Diego?
Do you think that we're done
giving you a hard time?
You're the only one here
who still believes
we should be scared of you, Emilia.
But the truth is,
you're the one who's scared!
Because the moment justice prevails,
you'll get what you deserve.
Wow!
I'm so scared.
Can you believe that, Auntie?
They had a lot to say. They talk too much!
All I asked was if
she was Lily Cruz, right?
-[Arnaldo] So, let's go?
-[Emilia] Let's go!
They're so irritating!
-Good morning, Congressman.
-Good morning.
[grunts]
Congressman.
Don't touch me!
[tense music playing]
That was one of the Jaguar's men!
He's here! The Jaguar's here!
Where's Arnaldo?! Where is he?!
-He's upstairs, Congressman.
-Get him!
And get him out of
this building! Right now!
Yes, you're right.
The peace treaty was my idea.
But, of course, that doesn't mean
we'll really patch things up
with the Ardientes.
That will never happen.
Naturally, Anna, Emilia has
wanted to have you killed
since you made the revelation.
But that peace agreement
is the only thing
stopping her from killing you.
Ivy, we know the Ardientes well.
They don't keep their word.
They're just going with
this peace treaty agreement.
We shouldn't let our guard down.
Leave the security
of the headquarters to me.
I'll teach the volunteers
that Mister Pandoy brought in.
[Diego] We can't let them have
the advantage over us.
I'll work harder on the campaign,
and I'll make sure that we win.
Do what you need to do.
Anna.
Were you all right back there?
I already told you
you're getting yourself
into something serious.
You'll need this.
Jepoy, you will teach Anna
how to use this.
You need that gun.
You need to protect yourself.
Diego and Jepoy…
I want you two to protect Anna.
She's important to me.
So, she should never be harmed by anyone.
You can count on us.
How about you, Ivy?
After everything that happened,
are you still marrying Arnaldo?
Yes.
The wedding must push through.
It needs to push through.
I would like you to take care
of one of our enemies.
Kill Jaguar for the sake of our family.
Ping!
Thank you for coming here today
for the Poblacion Ardiente public debate.
You haven't been in
any government position before.
Wouldn't it be better if our lives
all improved together?
You're running out of time, Mayor.
Mayor?
[Ivy] I think it's time
the public found out
that my future husband
is going through something.
What do you mean?
Is the Mayor sick?
[tense music playing]